A loved story.
Celeste & Jesse Forever is a comedy, drama, romance
film directed by Lee Toland Krieger.
Celeste and Jesse met in high school and got married young.
They laugh at the same jokes and finish each other’s sentences.
They are forever linked in their friends’ minds as the perfect couple – she, a high-powered
businesswoman and budding novelist; he, a free spirit who keeps things from getting boring.
Their only problem is that they have decided to get divorced.
Can their perfect relationship withstand this minor setback?
Celeste Martin, played by Rashida Jones.
Jesse Abrams, played by Andy Samberg.
Beth, played by Ari Graynor.
Tucker, played by Eric Christian Olsen.
Paul, played by Chris Messina.
Riley Banks, played by Emma Roberts.
Celeste and Jesse Forever is a 2012 American romantic comedy-drama film directed by Lee Toland Krieger, written by Rashida Jones and Will McCormack, and
starring Jones and Andy Samberg alongside Chris Messina, Ari Graynor, Eric Christian Olsen, Will McCormack, Elijah Wood, and Emma Roberts.
The film was released on August 3, 2012, in New York City and Los Angeles.
The film explores themes of relationship problems,
divorce, mumblecore, friends in love.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.